Exactly one and a half years ago from today, you can see here that
we had made a video on
how to make ICICI credit card bill payment, that too in an instant way, so
it was quite effective and you
can see the date here, this is a video of 13th November 2023
and in this we had told that how
you will make payment through UPI
and that money gets credited instantly
within a few seconds, that is, the
same thing was told in the credit card
but this system has
stopped working now, so this process has
stopped.  You don't have to worry about this.
In this we will change the process a little.  The
rest of the system will remain the same
and your money will be paid as it was before.
let's watch.
We made a payment on 6th May at 10:12
which is a transaction of ₹1 here and if
you go and
see the same transaction in ICICI's IM mobile application, there
is ₹1 credit there.  Now we are going to
show you live what you have to do.
Now, to make payment here, it is
not necessary that you will be able to do it only through PhonePe.
You can also do it through Paytm, you
can do it through Google Pay.  Everyone's function is the same.
But for now, let us tell you about PhonePe.  The
interface of PhonePe has already
changed.  Therefore, you have to click on To Mobile Number or
To Contact.
Ok?  As soon as you click here, you will see the
search option that appears here,
you have to go into it.  And
what do you want to write here?  Earlier, we had to
enter the 16 digit card number.
After that this had to be done @ ICICI.
Now the format here will be
CCP. Your 10 digit mobile number, okay
10 digit mobile number, after that the
last four digits of your
credit card number, you have to enter that here,
after that @
ICICI, after doing this, as soon as you tap on it, the
beneficiary UPI ID will
appear here and as you verify,
see here my name has appeared here
Ghulam Gaus, after that you have to click on save,
as soon as you click on save,
you will see here that the option to make payment has appeared.
Now here we have already done ₹1 once.
After that we are shooting this video.
After that, all you have to do is make the
payment here.
Now here we have to see whether this money has been
credited or not.  To get credit, go to
My Card.  We click here.
Now let us check whether the money has been credited here or
not.  Take a look here.
You can see here on the 7th date that the
₹10 payment which we have just made has
arrived here.  This means
that the process is the same.  All you have to do is
enter the complete card number, you do
n't have to enter the complete card number.
There you have to enter your registered mobile number.
And you have to enter the last four digits of the
card number.
@ ICICI tax has to be paid, the
format of which can be seen here